http://www.crumlin.org/privacy

Privacy Statement
Crumlin Sportmen's Association is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful
and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Crumlin Sportmen's Association Web site and governs data
collection and usage. By using the Crumlin Sportmen's Association website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Crumlin Sportmen's Association collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, work address or telephone number. Crumlin Sportmen's Association also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP/Postal code, preferences.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Crumlin Sportmen's Association. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Crumlin Sportmen's Association for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Crumlin Sportmen's Association Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Crumlin Sportmen's Association public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Crumlin Sportmen's Association does not read any of your private online communications.
Crumlin Sportmen's Association encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Crumlin Sportmen's Association so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information.
Crumlin Sportmen's Association is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Crumlin Sportmen's Association and Crumlin Sportmen's Association family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Crumlin Sportmen's Association collects and uses your personal information to operate the Crumlin Sportmen's Association
Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Crumlin Sportmen's Association also uses your personally identifiable
information to inform you of other products or services available from Crumlin Sportmen's Association and its affiliates.
Crumlin Sportmen's Association may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Crumlin Sportmen's Association does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Crumlin Sportmen's Association
may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Crumlin Sportmen's Association may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries.
All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Crumlin Sportmen's Association, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Crumlin Sportmen's Association does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political
affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Crumlin Sportmen's Association keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Crumlin Sportmen's Association,
in order to determine what Crumlin Sportmen's Association services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized
content and advertising within Crumlin Sportmen's Association to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested
in a particular subject area.
Crumlin Sportmen's Association Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Crumlin Sportmen's Association or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Crumlin Sportmen's Association; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Crumlin Sportmen's Association, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Crumlin Sportmen's Association Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text
file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your
computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the crumlin purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell
the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Crumlin Sportmen's Association pages,
or register with Crumlin Sportmen's Association site or services, a cookie helps Crumlin Sportmen's Association to recall your
specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing
addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Crumlin Sportmen's Association Web site, the information
you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Crumlin Sportmen's Association features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify
your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience
the interactive features of the Crumlin Sportmen's Association services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Crumlin Sportmen's Association secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.
Crumlin Sportmen's Association secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled,
secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Crumlin Sportmen's Association will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback.
Crumlin Sportmen's Association encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Crumlin Sportmen's Association is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Crumlin Sportmen's Association welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy.  If you believe that Crumlin Sportmen's Association has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Crumlin Sportmen's Association through out contact page.  We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Terms of Use
Copyright © 2020 Crumlin Sportsmen's Association
Privacy Statement
